# **Arnold Bustamante**

# **UX/UI** Designer

arnoldbustamante.design | linkedin.com/in/arnold-bustamante arnoldbustamante@gmail.com | (718) 730-0827 New York, NY

## **PROFILE**

UX/UI Designer proficient in UX research and visual design. With over 8 years of customer service experience, was able to develop a deep knowledge in user empathy, team collaboration and strategic thinking. Strong background in acting and improv.

#### **PROJECTS**

**Movement** | *iOS Application* | *View at arnoldbustamante.design* Created a health and fitness tracker to help users reach their fitness goals. The app gives users the ability to track their personal health and fitness progress, log custom workouts, and even discover new workouts.

**CORE** | Web Application | View at arnoldbustamante.design Created a cloud file manager service designed for filmmakers. It gives the artist the ability to create, share and upload various files.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Bloc Immersive UX/UI Program | Dec 2019 - Jul 2020

- Alongside a senior product designer, learned industry best practices and design process standards with a focus on UX research, visual design, and front-end development.
- Produced a clickable prototype of a cloud file management app dedicated to empowering filmmakers.
- Created a solution that allowed users of a public transit app to know what time a certain bus was arriving at a certain station.
- Conducted both in-person and remote usability tests in order to enhance the usability and functionality of a project.

#### Queens College | Sep 2011 - Apr 2012

• 30 credits towards a bachelor degree.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

The Meatball Shop | Bartender | Oct 2015 - Dec 2019

 Increase sales by utilizing data acquired through customer interactions.

### Banana Republic | Cashier/ Sales Associate | Nov 2012 - Oct 2015

• Collaborated with managers and team members to achieve the company's daily sales goals.

# **SKILLS**

#### UX & UI

- Surveys
- Interviews
- Competitive analysis
- User stories
- User Personas
- · User flows
- Site maps
- · Usability testing
- Branding
- Wireframing
- Prototyping

#### **Software**

- Figma
- Whimsical
- Atom
- GitHub

# Development

- HTML
- CSS
- Basic JavaScript
- Basic jQuery